IQBAL KHAIRIL PUTRA

QUALITY ASSURANCE

PROFILE

Quality Assurance Specialist with more than 2 years of enterprise software product quality assurance experience including test planning implementation and execution. Talented in performance testing, competent in designing a prototype. Excellent at quickly identifying high level test strategies and problems. Collaborative but decisive personal style; effective communicator and problem solver.

EDUCATION

AMIKOM, Yogyakarta Bachelor Degree of Information System 2010-2015

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Microsoft Office
- Programming Language
- Operation Systems
- Networking
- Installation
- Troubleshooting
- Gaming
- Prototyping
- Game testing

CONTACT INFORMATION

Mobile: +628112951092

Email: igbalkhairil@outlook.com

Address: Jalan Dayu Baru I, No. 9A, Sinduharjo, Ngaqlik, Kabupaten Sleman, Daerah Istimewa

Yogyakarta 55581

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNT MANAGER

Mindo Small Business Solutions, May 2019 - Present

- Operating as the lead point of contact for any and all matters specific to your accounts
- Building and maintaining strong, long-lasting customer relationships
- Overseeing customer account management, including negotiating contracts and agreements to maximize profit

NON-TECHNICAL LEADER

Mindo Small Business Solutions, Dec 2018 - Present

 In charge with the specification and reviewing the specification of the project before development phase, and also, stay in touch with the client to decide or discuss about the specification of the project.

QUALITY ASSURANCE

Mindo Small Business Solutions, June 2017-Dec 2018

- Draft quality assurance policies and procedures
- Interpret and implement quality assurance standards
- Evaluate adequacy of quality assurance standards
- Devise sampling procedures and directions for recording and reporting quality data
- Review the implementation and efficiency of quality and inspection systems
- Plan, conduct and monitor testing and inspection of materials and products to ensure finished product quality
- Investigate customer complaints and non-conformance issues
- Collect and compile statistical quality data

GAME TESTER

Gameloft Indonesia, April 2016-June 2017

 Testing of computer and mobile games before they are released in order to spot any bugs that are present within the software and to suggest improvements to the gameplay.